Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Marketing Files, 1994-2015; 10
  - General Marketing Files, 11.1
    - Hetherington; Guerrilla Auditors, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hetherington; Original Review Slips, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hetherington; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hetherington; Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Migrants and Migration in Modern North America, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Original Review Sheet, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; S'11, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoerder; World Migrations in the Second Millennium, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - HOFFMAN & MURPHY: Essentials of the Theory of Fiction, 1995-2003 (Box 80)
    - Hoffman & Murphy 2nd Ed.: Review Slip, 1996 (Box 80)
    - Hoffman; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoffman; Cover Copy, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoffman; Original Review Slips, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoffman; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoffman; Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hoffman; The War Machines, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hong; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hong; Cover Copy, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hong; Original Review Slips, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hong; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hong; Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hong; Strange Affinities, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Hurley; Ads, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Hurley; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Hurley; Publicity, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Hurley; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Hurley; Reviews, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Hurley; Revolutionary Suicide and Other Desperate Measures, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Jackson, Michael Ads, 2007-2008 (Box 80)
    - Jackson, Michael Copy and Blurbs, 2007 (Box 80)
    - Jackson, Michael Orig. Review Slips, 2007 (Box 80)
    - Jackson, Michael Publicity, 2007 (Box 80)
    - Jackson, Michael Reviews, 2008-2009 (Box 80)
    - Jackson, Michael; Excursions, 2006-2008 (Box 80)
    - Jacquette: c; Institutions, Resources, 2004-2007 (Box 80)
    - Jacquette Ads, 2006 (Box 80)
    - Jacquette copy and blurbs, 2005-2006 (Box 80)
    - Jacquette Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 80)
    - Jacquette Publicity, 2006-2011 (Box 80)
    - Jacquette Reviews, 2006-2011 (Box 80)
    - Johnson; Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 86)
    - Johnson; Cover Copy and Blurbs, 2013 (Box 86)
    - Johnson; Original Review Slips, 2014 (Box 86)
    - Johnson; Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 86)
    - Johnson; Reviews, 2014 (Box 86)
    - Johnson; The Barbara Johnson Reader, 2013-2014 (Box 86)
    - Joseph; Ads and Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 86)
    - Joseph; Close Encounters of Empire, 1997-1999 (Box 86)
    - Joseph; Original Review Slip, 1998 (Box 86)
    - K.Davies, 2007 (Box 85)
    - Karen Beckman; Vanishing Women, 2002-2009 (Box 79)
    - Kavuri-Bauer; Ads, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kavuri-Bauer; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kavuri-Bauer; Monumental Matters, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kavuri-Bauer; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kavuri-Bauer; Publicity, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kavuri-Bauer; Reviews, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kester; Reviews, 2010 (Box 83)
    - Kester; Ads, 2010 (Box 83)
    - Kester; Original Review Slip, 2010 (Box 83)
    - Kester; The One and the Many, 2010 (Box 83)
    - Kester; The One and the Many, 2010 (Box 83)
    - Kim; Ads, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kim; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kim; Publicity, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kim; Reviews, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kim; Virtual Hallyu, 2011 (Box 83)
    - Kipnis; Ads and Reviews, 1999-2001 (Box 86)
    - Kipnis; Bound and Gagged: Pornography and the Politics of Fantasy in America, 1998-2003 (Box 86)
    - Kipnis; Original Review Slip, 1999 (Box 86)
    - Kirby; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Kirby; Original Review Slips, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Kirby; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Kirby; Quantum Anthropologies, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Kirby; Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Klinenberg, et al; ADS, 2001-2002 (Box 79)
    - Klinenberg, et al; Original Review Slip, 2001 (Box 79)
    - Klinenberg, et al; Publicity, 2001 (Box 79)
    - Klinenberg, et al; Reviews, 2001-2013 (Box 79)
    - Kolodny, 2007 (Box 87)
    - Kolodny; Ads, 2007 (Box 87)
    - Kolodny; Copy and Blurbs, 2006-2007 (Box 87)
    - Kolodny; Publicity, 2006-2007 (Box 87)
    - Kolodny; Original Review Slip, 2007 (Box 87)
    - Kolodny; Reviews, 2007 (Box 87)
    - Kolodny; The Life and Tradition of the Red Man, 2007-2008 (Box 87)
    - Laderman; Ads, 2009-2010 (Box 86)
    - Laderman; Cover Copy, 2008 (Box 86)
    - Laderman; Original Review Slip, 2009 (Box 86)
    - Laderman; Reviews, 2009-2010 (Box 86)
    - Laderman; Tours of Vietnam, 2008-2010 (Box 86)
    - Lebow; Ads, 2007 (Box 86)
    - Lebow; Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Lebow; Publicity, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Lebow; Reviews, 2006-2007 (Box 86)
    - Lebow; Copy and Blurbs, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Lebow; The Politics of Memory in Postwar Europe, 2005-2006 (Box 86)
    - Longinovic; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Longinovic; Cover Copy, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Longinovic; Publicity, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Longinovic; Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Longinovic; Vampire Nation, 2010-2011 (Box 83)
    - Lucey; Ads, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Lucey; Copy and Blurbs, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Lucey; Original Review Slip, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Lucey; Publicity, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Lucey; Reviews, 2004-2007 (Box 86)
    - Lucey; The Misfit of the Family, 2001-2004 (Box 86)
    - Manalansan; Ads, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Manalansan; Copy and Blurbs, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Manalansan; Global Divas, 2003-2004 (Box 86)
    - Manalansan; Original Review Slip, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Manalansan; Publicity, 2003 (Box 86)
    - Manalansan; Reviews, 2003-2004 (Box 86)
    - Mao; Ads, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Mao; Bad Modernisms, 2005-2006 (Box 86)
    - Mao; Copy and Blurbs, 2005 (Box 86)
    - Mao; Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Mao; Publicity, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Mao; Reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 86)
    - McDuffie, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McDuffie; Ads, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McDuffie; Cover Copy, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McDuffie; Original Review Slips, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McDuffie; Publicity, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McDuffie; Reviews, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McDuffie; Sojourning for Freedom, 2010 (Box 83)
    - McHenry; Ads, 2002 (Box 86)
    - McHenry; Forgotten Readers, 2002 (Box 86)
    - McHenry; Reviews, 2003-2004 (Box 86)
    - Metzl: ads, 2003-2005 (Box 77)
    - Metzl: Freud & Prozac, 2002-2007 (Box 77)
    - Metzl: Original Review Slip, 2003 (Box 77)
    - Metzl: Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 77)
    - Metzl: Reviews, 2003-2005 (Box 77)
    - Metzl Copy and Blurbs, 2002-2003 (Box 77)
    - MICHAEL HOFFMAN & PATRICK MURPHY: Essentials of the Theory of Fiction ADS and REVIEWS, 1996-2006 (Box 80)
    - Mignolo; Ads, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mignolo; Original Review Slips, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Mignolo; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mignolo; Reviews, 2013 (Box 84)
    - Mignolo; Seed Copies, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mignolo; The Darker Side of Western Modernity, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Milton Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 77)
    - Milton, Cynthia: The Arts of Truth-telling in Post-Shining Path Peru, 2011-2013 (Box 77)
    - Milton/ Ads, 2014 (Box 77)
    - Milton/ Copy and Blurbs, 2013 (Box 77)
    - Milton/ Original Review Slip, 2014 (Box 77)
    - Milton/ Reviews, 2014 (Box 77)
    - Mirzoeff; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mirzoeff; Reviews, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mirzoeff; Ads, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mirzoeff; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Mirzoeff; The Right to Look, 2011 (Box 84)
    - MODERN GIRL Ads, 2009 (Box 77)
    - MODERN GIRL AROUND THE WORLD Research Group, 2006-2008 (Box 77)
    - MODERN GIRL Copy and Blurbs, 2008 (Box 77)
    - MODERN GIRL Orig. Review Slips, 2009 (Box 77)
    - MODERN GIRL Publicity, 2008-2013 (Box 77)
    - MODERN GIRL Reviews, 2009-2010 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty: Ads, 2003 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty: Feminism without Borders, 2002-2006 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty: Review Slip Original, 2003 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty: Reviews, 2003-2006 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty Copy and Blurbs, 2002-2003 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty Events, 2003 (Box 77)
    - Mohanty Publicity, 2003-2005 (Box 77)
    - Monk: Ads and Reviews, 2002-2004 (Box 77)
    - Monk: Publicity, 2001-2002 (Box 77)
    - Monk: The Aesthetic Occupation, 2000-2004 (Box 77)
    - Monk Events, 2002 (Box 77)
    - Monk Original Review Slip, 2002 (Box 77)
    - Morris: Hong Kong Connections, 2005-2006 (Box 77)
    - Morris Ads, 2006-2007 (Box 77)
    - Morris Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Morris Publicity, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Morris Reviews, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Muller; Ads, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Muller; Musical Echoes, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Muller; Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Muller; Reviews, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Murphy Ads, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Murphy Copy and Blurbs, 2005 (Box 77)
    - Murphy Publicity, 2005-2013 (Box 77)
    - Murphy Reviews, 2007-2014 (Box 77)
    - Murphy, Michelle; Inside Sick Building Syndrome, 2004-2007 (Box 77)
    - Murphy, Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Myers: painting culture, 2001-2004 (Box 77)
    - Myers ADS, 2003-2005 (Box 77)
    - Myers Event, 2003 (Box 77)
    - Myers original review slips, 2002-2003 (Box 77)
    - Myers Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 77)
    - Naficy; Ads, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Ads, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Artisanal Cinema, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Industrializing National Cinema, 2010-2011 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Naficy; Reviews, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Ni; Ads and Reviews, 2003-2005 (Box 87)
    - Ni; Memoirs from the Beijing Film Academy, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Ni; Original Review Slips, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Ni; Publicity, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Nugent; Ads, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Nugent; Government and Politics of the European Union, 2001-2005 (Box 87)
    - Nugent; Original Review Slips, 2003 (Box 87)
    - Nugent; Publicity, 2003-2006 (Box 87)
    - ORIGINAL REVIEW SLIP, 1999 (Box 80)
    - Paillalef; Ads, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Paillalef; Original Review Slip, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Paillalef; Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Paillalef; Publicity, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Paillalef; What a Flower is Reborn, 2001-2003 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Cover Copy, 2009 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Original Review Slip, 2009 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Publicity, 2009-2010 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Ads, 2010 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Reviews, 2009-2012 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Seed Copies, 2009 (Box 87)
    - Paredez; Selenidad.., 2008-2010 (Box 87)
    - Parks; Ads, 2004-2005 (Box 87)
    - Parks; Copy and Blurbs, 2004-2005 (Box 87)
    - Parks; Cultures in Orbit.., 2004-2005 (Box 87)
    - Parks; Original Review Slip, 2005 (Box 87)
    - Parks; Publicity, 2005 (Box 87)
    - Parks; Reviews, 2005-2007 (Box 87)
    - Perry; Ads, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Perry; Original Review Slips, 2001 (Box 87)
    - Perry; Publicity, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Perry; Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Perry; Shades of White, 2001-2004 (Box 87)
    - Pilkey; Ads, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Pilkey; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Pilkey; On Science, Liars, and Deniers, 2009-2011 (Box 84)
    - Pilkey; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Pilkey; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Pinney and Peterson; Ads, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Pinney and Peterson; Copy and Blurbs, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Pinney and Peterson; Reviews, 2003-2005 (Box 87)
    - Pinney and Peterson; Original Review Slip, 2003 (Box 87)
    - Pinney and Peterson; Photography's Other Histories, 2002-2004 (Box 87)
    - Pinney and Peterson; Publicity, 2003-2005 (Box 87)
    - Polan; Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 84)
    - Polan; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Polan; Julia Child's The French Chef, 2010-2011 (Box 84)
    - Polan; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Polan; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Polan; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Povinelli; Ads, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Povinelli; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Povinelli; Economies of Abandonment, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Povinelli; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Povinelli; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Povinelli; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Rademacher; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Rademacher; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Rademacher; Ads, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Rademacher; Reigning the River, 2010-2011 (Box 84)
    - Rademacher; Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 84)
    - Reddy; Ads, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Reddy; Freedom with Violence, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Reddy; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Reddy; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Reddy; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Retman; Ads, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Retman; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Retman; Fictions of the Folk in the Great Depression, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Retman; Original Review Slips, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Retman; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Retman; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Review Slip Originals, 1996 (Box 81)
    - Reviews and Ads, 1996-1999 (Box 81)
    - Ridgeway Ads (Box 81)
    - Ridgeway copy and blurbs, 2004 (Box 81)
    - Ridgeway Original Review Slip, 2004 (Box 81)
    - Ridgeway Publicity, 2004-2005 (Box 81)
    - Ridgeway Reviews, 2005 (Box 81)
    - Ridgeway, James / Who owns the Earth?, 2003-2005 (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg and Harding / Histories of the Future, 2004-2006 (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg ads, 2005 (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg copy and blurbs, 2004 (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg original review slip, 2005 (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg publicity, 2004-2006 (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg reviews, 2005-2008 (Box 81)
    - Saikia; Ads, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Saikia; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Saikia; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Saikia; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Saikia; Reviews, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Saikia; Women, War, and the Making of Bangladesh: Remembering 1971, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - SCHMITT ADS (Box 81)
    - SCHMITT COPY and BLURBS, 2003 (Box 81)
    - SCHMITT ORIGINAL REVIEW SLIP, 2004 (Box 81)
    - SCHMITT PUBLICITY, 2004-2014 (Box 81)
    - SCHMITT REVIEWS, 2004-2008 (Box 81)
    - Schmitt; Legality and Legitimacy, 2004-2007 (Box 81)
    - Schweppenhauser Cover Copy, 2009 (Box 81)
    - Schweppenhauser Ads, 2009 (Box 81)
    - Schweppenhauser Original Review Slip, 2009 (Box 81)
    - Schweppenhauser Publicity, 2009-2010 (Box 81)
    - Schweppenhauser Reviews, 2009-2011 (Box 81)
    - Schweppenhauser, Gerhard -c; Theodor W. Adorno, 2006-2010 (Box 81)
    - Sedgwick: ads, 2002-2003 (Box 81)
    - Sedgwick: original review slip, 2003 (Box 81)
    - Sedgwick: reviews, 2003-2012 (Box 81)
    - Sedgwick and Frank: Shame and its Sisters, 1994-2010 (Box 81)
    - Sedgwick S8 Publicity, 2002-2011 (Box 81)
    - Sedgwick/ Touching Feeling, 2002-2005 (Box 81)
    - Sharma, 2006-2007 (Box 81)
    - Sharma Ads, 2008-2009 (Box 81)
    - Sharma Cover Copy, 2008-2009 (Box 81)
    - Sharma Original Review Slip, 2009 (Box 81)
    - Sharma Publicity, 2009 (Box 81)
    - Sharma Reviews, 2009 (Box 81)
    - Sharma, Pandley; Chocolate, 2005-2010 (Box 81)
    - Sharma; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Sharma; Ads, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Sharma; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Sharma; Empire's Garden. Assam and the Making of India, 2010-2011 (Box 84)
    - Sharma; Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Sharma; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Shukla and Tinsman Ads, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Shukla and Tinsman Copy and Blurbs, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Shukla and Tinsman Final Publication; Imagining.., 2007 (Box 81)
    - Shukla and Tinsman Original Review Slips, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Shukla and Tinsman Publicity, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Shukla and Tinsman Reviews, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Smilde; Ads, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Smilde; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Smilde; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Smilde; Venezuela's Bolivarian Democracy, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Soares; Ads, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Soares; Catholic Africans in Colonial Brazil, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Soares; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Soares; Original Review Slips, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Soares; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Soares; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 84)
    - Springer; Ads, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Springer; Copy and Blurbs, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Springer; Living.., 2005-2006 (Box 81)
    - Springer; Original Review Slip, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Springer; Publicity, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Springer; Reviews, 2007 (Box 81)
    - Steinmetz; Ads, 2006 (Box 81)
    - Steinmetz; Copy and Blurbs, 2006 (Box 81)
    - Steinmetz; Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 81)
    - Steinmetz; Publicity, 2006 (Box 81)
    - Steinmetz; Reviews, 2006 (Box 81)
    - Steinmetz; The Politics, 2005-2006 (Box 81)
    - Stern, Steve; Pinochet's Chile PB, 2006-2012 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Battling... Ads, 2005 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Battling... Copy and Blurbs, 2006-2010 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Battling... Original Review Slip, 2007-2009 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Battling... Publicity, 2007-2010 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Battling... Reviews, 2006 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Pinochet's Chile Ads, 2006 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Pinochet's Chile Copy and Blurbs, 1998-2002 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Pinochet's Chile Publicity, 2007-2010 (Box 78)
    - Stern; Pinochet's Chile Reviews, 2006-2012 (Box 78)
    - STOLZOFF, 2000-2001 (Box 78)
    - STOLZOFF: EVENTS, 2002-2006 (Box 78)
    - Stolzoff:┬áWake the Town & Tell the People, 2000-2001 (Box 78)
    - Stolzoff au brochure, 1999-2005 (Box 78)
    - Stolzoff Continued; Ads and Reviews, 1999-2011 (Box 78)
    - Stolzoff Review Slip Original & Advance Praise Sheet, 1999-2000 (Box 78)
    - Striffler & Moberg, editors; Bananas, Conflict, and Cap., 2003-2004 (Box 78)
    - Striffler and Moberg copy and blurbs, 2003-2004 (Box 78)
    - Striffler and Moberg orig. review slip, 2003 (Box 78)
    - Striffler and Moberg publicity, 2004-2006 (Box 78)
    - Striffler and Moberg reviews, 2002-2005 (Box 78)
    - Striffler and Moberg ads, 2003 (Box 78)
    - Striffler Reviews, 2004-2006 (Box 78)
    - Tasker; Ads, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Tasker; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Tasker; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Tasker; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Tasker; Reviews, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Tasker; Soldier's Stories.., 2010-2011 (Box 84)
    - Thomas ads, 2004-2009 (Box 78)
    - Thomas copy & blurbs, 2004-2009 (Box 78)
    - Thomas org. review slip, 2007 (Box 78)
    - Thomas publicity, 2004 (Box 78)
    - Thomas reviews, 2008-2010 (Box 78)
    - Thomas, Nicholas, Anna Cole, and Brownen Douglas eds. -c; Tatau/Tattoo: Bodies, Art, and Exchange, 2005 (Box 78)
    - Thomas; Exceptional Violence, 2010-2012 (Box 84)
    - Thomas; Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Thomas; Publicity, 2011 (Box 84)
    - Thomas; Reviews, 2012 (Box 84)
    - Tutino: Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Tutino; Ads, 2012 (Box 85)
    - Tutino; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Tutino; Making a New World, 2010-2011 (Box 85)
    - Tutino; Publicity, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Tutino; Reviews, 2011-2013 (Box 85)
    - Vanderwood Ads, 2010-2011 (Box 78)
    - Vanderwood cover copy, 2004-2010 (Box 78)
    - Vanderwood orig. review slips, 2010 (Box 78)
    - Vanderwood Publicity, 2009-2010 (Box 78)
    - Vanderwood Reviews, 2004-2007 (Box 78)
    - Vanderwood, Paul J.; Satan's Playground, 2009-2011 (Box 78)
    - Vaugh reviews, 2008-2010 (Box 78)
    - Vaughan, Creating the Creole Island, 2005 (Box 78)
    - Vaughn ads, 2004 (Box 78)
    - Vaughn copy & blurbs, 2005-2007 (Box 78)
    - Vaughn original review slip, 2004-2006 (Box 78)
    - Vaughn publicity, 2005 (Box 78)
    - Vilaca Ads, 2005-2008 (Box 78)
    - Vilaca cover copy, 2010 (Box 78)
    - Vilaca orig. review slips, 2010-2013 (Box 78)
    - Vilaca Reviews, 2010-2011 (Box 78)
    - Vilaca, Aparecida; Quem Somos Nos / Who We Are, 2010 (Box 78)
    - Vilaca Publicity, 2010 (Box 78)
    - Wald ads, 2007 (Box 78)
    - Wald copy and blurbs, 2007 (Box 78)
    - Wald original review slip, 2007-2009 (Box 78)
    - Wald Publicity, 2008-2010 (Box 78)
    - Wald reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 78)
    - Wald Seed Copies, 2008 (Box 78)
    - Wald, Priscilla; Contagion, 2007 (Box 78)
    - Waldby; Ads, 2006 (Box 87)
    - Waldby; Copy and Blurbs, 2005 (Box 87)
    - Waldby; Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 87)
    - Waldby; Publicity, 2005-2006 (Box 87)
    - Waldby; Reviews, 2007 (Box 87)
    - Waldby; Tissue Economics, 2005-2007 (Box 87)
    - Way; Ads, 2012 (Box 87)
    - Way; Original Review Slip, 2012 (Box 87)
    - Way; Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 87)
    - Way; Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 87)
    - Way; The Mayan in the Mall, 2011 (Box 87)
    - Weeks; Ads, 2011-2012 (Box 85)
    - Weeks; Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Weeks; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Weeks; Publicity, 2011-2013 (Box 85)
    - Weeks; Reviews, 2011-2013 (Box 85)
    - Weeks; The Problem with Work, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Weintraub; Ads and Reviews, 2002-2004 (Box 88)
    - Weintraub; Au Brochure, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Weintraub; How Economics Became a Mathematical Science, 2002-2004 (Box 88)
    - Weintraub; Original Review Slip, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Weintraub; Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
    - Weiss; Ads and Review, 2001-2002 (Box 88)
    - Weiss; Original Review Slip, 2001 (Box 88)
    - Weiss; The New Trail, 2000-2001 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Ads, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Hit Me, Fred, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Hit Me, Fred, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Original Review Slip, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wesley; Photos, 1993 (Box 88)
    - White; Original Review Slip, 2001 (Box 88)
    - White; Reviews, 2001-2002 (Box 88)
    - White; Ads, 2002 (Box 88)
    - White; Developments in Russian Politics 5, 2000-2001 (Box 88)
    - Wiegman; Ads, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
    - Wiegman; Original Review Slip, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wiegman; Publicity, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wiegman; Reviews, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Wiegman; Women's Studies On Its Own, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Willey; Harnessing Farms and Forests in the Low-Carbon Economy, 2004-2007 (Box 88)
    - Willey; Original Review Slip, 2007 (Box 88)
    - Willey; Publicity, 2007 (Box 88)
    - Willey; Reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 88)
    - Wirth; Original Review Slip, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Wirth; Gay Rebel of the Harlem Renaissance, 2001-2002 (Box 87)
    - Wirth; Materials from the Author, 1999-2001 (Box 87)
    - Wirth; Publicity, 2002 (Box 87)
    - Wirth; Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 87)
    - Zilberg; Reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 85)
    - Zilberg; Ads, 2011-2012 (Box 85)
    - Zilberg; Gangster, Cop, Soldier, Spy: The Many Faces of Transnational Violence.., 2011 (Box 85)
    - Zilberg; Original Review Slip, 2011 (Box 85)
    - Zilberg; Publicity, 2011 (Box 85)
  - Emily Young Files, 11.2
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '04 as of Fall '11, 2004-2011 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '07 as of Fall '10, 2007-2010 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '08 as of Fall '10, 2008-2010 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '09 as of Fall '10, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '10: Bday Reports, 2010 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Spring '10: Bday Reports, 2010 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '08 as of Fall '09, 2008-2009 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '07 as of Fall '09, 2007-2009 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Fall '06 as of Fall '09, 2006-2009 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Spring '08 as of Spring '09, 2008-2009 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Spring '07 as of Spring '09, 2007-2009 (Box 22)
    - Birthday Reports 2007-2011: Spring '06 as of Spring '09, 2006-2009 (Box 22)